[
    {
        "Question": "prodigious",
        "Answer": "massive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "profile",
        "Answer": "view from side",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "profound",
        "Answer": "intense",
        "Options": "far-reaching"
    },
    {
        "Question": "progressive",
        "Answer": "increasing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prohibit",
        "Answer": "prevent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "projected",
        "Answer": "shown",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "proliferation",
        "Answer": "growth",
        "Options": "increase"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prolonged",
        "Answer": "extended",
        "Options": "lengthy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "promote",
        "Answer": "encourage",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prone",
        "Answer": "likely ",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pronounced",
        "Answer": "strongest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pronouncement",
        "Answer": "statement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "propagated",
        "Answer": "spread",
        "Options": "multiply"
    },
    {
        "Question": "properly",
        "Answer": "appropriately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "properties",
        "Answer": "characteristics",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "propose",
        "Answer": "offer the theory",
        "Options": "suggest"
    },
    {
        "Question": "propulsion",
        "Answer": "moving forward",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prospect",
        "Answer": "possibility",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "provided",
        "Answer": "if",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "provided that",
        "Answer": "as long as",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "provoked",
        "Answer": "brought about",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "proximity",
        "Answer": "closeness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "puncture",
        "Answer": "pierce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pursue",
        "Answer": "practice",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "quantifiable",
        "Answer": "measurable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "quest",
        "Answer": "search",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "radical",
        "Answer": "extreme",
        "Options": "fundamental"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ratio",
        "Answer": "proportion",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "raw",
        "Answer": "uncooked",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "readily",
        "Answer": "easily",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "reasonable",
        "Answer": "sufficient",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rebound",
        "Answer": "recovery",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "redundancy",
        "Answer": "duplication",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "refined",
        "Answer": "improved",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "regarded",
        "Answer": "considered",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "regrettably",
        "Answer": "unfortunately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "regulating",
        "Answer": "controlling",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "reinforce",
        "Answer": "strengthen",
        "Options": "supporting"
    },
    {
        "Question": "rekindled",
        "Answer": "renewed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "related",
        "Answer": "connected",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "relatively",
        "Answer": "comparatively",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "relentless",
        "Answer": "unceasing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "relics",
        "Answer": "remains",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "reluctant",
        "Answer": "unwilling",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rely",
        "Answer": "depend",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "remarkable",
        "Answer": "extraordinary",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "remarkably close",
        "Answer": "extremely close",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "remnants",
        "Answer": "remainders",
        "Options": "remains"
    },
    {
        "Question": "remote",
        "Answer": "distant",
        "Options": "isolated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "renown",
        "Answer": "fame",
        "Options": "famous"
    },
    {
        "Question": "representative",
        "Answer": "typical",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "repudiate",
        "Answer": "reject",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "repulicate",
        "Answer": "reproduce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "retarding",
        "Answer": "slowing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "resemble",
        "Answer": "look like",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "resistance",
        "Answer": "opposition",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "resolve",
        "Answer": "find a solution for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "respectively",
        "Answer": "separately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "restricted",
        "Answer": "limited",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "resume",
        "Answer": "restart",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "revered",
        "Answer": "honored",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "reveal",
        "Answer": "show",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "revised",
        "Answer": "changed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rice-deficient portions",
        "Answer": "the parts that do not have enough rice",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rigors",
        "Answer": "difficulties",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ritual",
        "Answer": "ceremonial",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rival",
        "Answer": "competing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "robust",
        "Answer": "healthy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rotates",
        "Answer": "alternates",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "roughly",
        "Answer": "approximately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rudimentary",
        "Answer": "basic",
        "Options": "undeveloped"
    },
    {
        "Question": "sacred",
        "Answer": "holy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scale",
        "Answer": "size",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scarcity",
        "Answer": "lack",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scattered",
        "Answer": "widely separated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scenario",
        "Answer": "situation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scores",
        "Answer": "large numbers",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "securing",
        "Answer": "getting",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "seek",
        "Answer": "attempt",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "segregated",
        "Answer": "separated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sensible",
        "Answer": "reasonable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sentimental",
        "Answer": "emotional",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sequence",
        "Answer": "series",
        "Options": "order"
    },
    {
        "Question": "sequentially",
        "Answer": "one after another",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "several simultaneous developments",
        "Answer": "developments that occurred at the same time",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "severe",
        "Answer": "extreme",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "severed",
        "Answer": "cut off",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "severity",
        "Answer": "harshness",
        "Options": "seriousness"
    },
    {
        "Question": "shifts",
        "Answer": "changes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "shortcoming",
        "Answer": "weakness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "signal",
        "Answer": "communicate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "signature",
        "Answer": "identifying mark",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "significant",
        "Answer": "considerable",
        "Options": "important"
    },
    {
        "Question": "signifying",
        "Answer": "indicating",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "similarly",
        "Answer": "likewise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "simultaneously",
        "Answer": "at the same time",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "size up",
        "Answer": "evaluate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "skeptical",
        "Answer": "doubtful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "slight",
        "Answer": "small",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sloping",
        "Answer": "inclining",
        "Options": ""
    }
]